Boy, does it feel good to be back.
And I hope it stays that way and I hope
it's
like this, like the good old days.
Cuz I miss them. So, Titan X community,
what's up? I hope you're having an
amazing I hope I hope you've had an
amazing couple of what you 1 2 years, I
think it's been.
Um
and
hopefully you're doing good right now.
I want to talk about something that
caught my attention. And I've been
holding back a little bit just because I
want to give it time to sink in a little
bit and have it I guess some people call
it marinate. Let it cook a little bit.
And I think it's time. So, shout out to
everybody that made this website. It is
buildify.win.
I will leave the link in the description
down below.
I'm not getting sponsored by the
website, okay? So,
dude and everybody else behind the whole
website, I appreciate you guys for that
live stream. I've been checking out on
the sidelines what you've been cooking
and honestly I respect it. A lot of
hustle, a lot of development time, money
and all that came into
uh this site.
Wow, I'm just now noticing that it's
Titan Z. That's funny.
Um but yeah, I want to cover a certain
token
that launched on this website
on buildify.win.
And I want to talk about it, okay?
These guys are OGs, like the OGs OGs.
Like I wasn't Well, I still technically
am. I know I don't make any YouTube
videos about Titan X anymore daily.
Every now and then I do one, but not as
like it was before.
>> [clears throat]
>> And
the OGs are still here. They are still
developing, doing their own thing,
bringing in the eco the community and
the ecosystem together to thrive
together. And there's one certain coin
that is standing out right now.
And ladies and gentlemen, that is Titan
X
Spartans.
Let me tell you.
This is still
a very
early and nice coin
that it could still see some gains. I
will leave this
token
down below in the description. You do
need Ethereum. I would recommend you
creating a fresh new wallet. I would
recommend you, you know, just putting in
a couple bucks. Of course, everybody's
financial status is different. 333
likes is actually very impressive. It is
paired with Titan X. If you don't know
what Titan X is, you need to do some
research. Um they do have the current
vault balance of 8.5 million dollars,
which hopefully the V1 slow release gets
activated and we get some Ethereum to
buy and burn Titan X. And because if it
since it is paired with Titan X,
then Titan X Spartans
will also see that run-up. If this pair
right here is very very nice.
As long as everything plays out
correctly, okay? I'm not saying the buy
and burn is going to activate tomorrow.
It could be months, it could be years,
okay? But whenever it does and all the
millions of dollars of Titan X
uh comes on through the Ethereum,
it can send TitanX Spartans on over to a
crazy run. Now, I want to zoom out onto
the daily chart. Look at this.
We've already seen some very impressive
run-ups. Uh, I think I can only go down
to there. So, three, four, five zeros
and a nine. And it went as high as four
zeros and a five. So, it's already had a
really nice run-up. And what you guys
don't know is that this pullback is
looking like it's on a support zone
right here within this zone. So, that
buying opportunity is literally here or
down below, I want to say in that four
zeros and a three four. So, it's very
close. Right now, it's at four zeros.
434. Market cap, ladies and gentlemen,
19.13.
24-hour volume just under $1,000.
And the
impressive thing
is not only is it just ranked number one
out of this whole entire thing, which by
the way, dude, if you are watching the
one of the devs,
dude,
please
verify, certify, you know, check mark
TitanX Spartans. I ask you for it
because I also want to launch my coin
that is paired with TitanX Spartans.
So, if you're listening, if you're
watching, um, do me a solid, please.
Let's verify some of these people. Of
course, step Let's go through the right
steps and and all that. So, that way we
can do it the right way and protect
people. But, let's go ahead and verify
Titan Spartans. Make it happen. So, that
way I can also feel safer about
launching a token on paired with
Spartans as well.
So, that way we can all of us can
succeed. So, right now
the tokenomics behind this Well, let me
read the description. TitanX Spartans is
a battle-ready community coin forged for
holders who believe in unity, strength,
and long-term conviction. Built around a
Spartan-inspired theme, it represents a
shield wall of believers moving together
with power, discipline, and purpose.
Founder is Crypto Connoisseur and Crypto
Conno 888. So, these two guys did hit me
up to be able to provide this YouTube
video. Shout-out to them. Um
and what I like is that they are the
OGs.
People that are holding this coin and
that's and that decided to get into this
coin
are the most dedicated, diamond-hands,
trustworthy people that there are. I
think there's like 50-something holders?
Yeah, 54. Right now, three people are
watching this.
Yeah, like that's the good thing about
them. You don't have to worry about the
the two main guys dumping on you. Very
trustworthy guys. Um I trust them and I
hope the TitanX community knows and
knows them as well and trust them. I'm
pretty sure we all know who that is.
Like there's a bunch of OGs, man.
There's
um Weapon Head as well, man. Shout-out
to you, my guy. Uh there's a bunch of
other ones out there that are still here
thriving, pushing TitanX, and all this
platform together. I'm hoping to do a a
live stream again. I don't mind it. So,
total supply right now, 441
million 119,225
TXS. The fair launch only lasted 8
hours, and that's it. The initial mint
price was one Ethereum could get you
about 1 billion TXS.
Additional tokens for liquidity pools
is, of course, 8%. There is a 28%
that went into this whole entire
purchases of ethereum and all that that
went into titanics primary builder do
get 3.5%
additional support is 5%
the buy and burn is 55.5%
ethereum leaderboard goes to 3% and the
titanics support is 5% with also a 3.33%
buy and sell tax
there is a burn of 45% 30 of that
percent goes to the token builder 10%
goes to the primary liquidity pool and
15% goes to external staking yeah so
platform models I don't you can't see it
cuz I'm on the way but this is all
having some good tokenomics it
understands it learned from titanics
some of this is very well made and
constructed I'm pretty sure they
thought about every percentage that the
tokenomics was based off of
was a very thought-out number to benefit
cuz any just one number off could really
throw the price and you can tell
that they
knew the rights and wrongs about what
not to do and what we we need to do to
succeed
now that's also you know all depending
on what titanics does all right please
guys do your research go follow them
their Twitter page is also
cryptoconausor and I think I think this
Twitter is also the same
I don't know I don't know about this one
but yeah man it's it looks
I miss you guys so much bro like I hope
the buy and burn does get turned on and
we all go back to fucking normal cuz it
does get a pain in the ass man like I
miss titanics plus there's nine almost,
you know, 8 and 1/2 million dollars just
sitting there. 4,400 Ethereum is fucking
wild. We need to use that. I wish we
could use it, you know, but then again,
I don't know.
Yeah, it is just it's been a wild ride.
It's been a wild couple of years. You
know, the whole Tinex ecosystem is
just I wouldn't say it's on pause cuz
it's still being developed. People are
still here doing their own thing,
buying, selling, trading, you know,
staking, burning. All this stuff is
still
some of this stuff, not everything, but
some of this stuff is still
doing some action. Like, the volume.
It's not like it was before,
but it's still something, you know, even
Dragonex is still creating something.
Um
oh, look, Tinex Spartans is actually
fourth. It's on Tinex Hub. I did not
know that. That's awesome.
Helios is a great one. Taurus, man, I
love Taurus.
Um
Blaze is still I think Blaze is still
doing their own like the website is
still good, if I'm not mistaken.
Yeah, like that's Baby Dragonex. Oof, I
love me some Baby Dragonex, bro.
So, it's still here, luckily. Um
who who was it that created the site?
Um
Shoot, I just had a huge brain fart.
Mike, there it is. Duh, it's right here.
Mike Dean, bro. What's up, buddy? I hope
you're doing good. I miss you guys.
So, yeah, check out the Tinex Spartans.
Uh I hope I didn't miss out anything,
but really, hey, 19.13
thousand dollars. 19.1 thousand dollars
of a market cap.
I mean, $1 million market cap will send
this what? 50x, right?
That'd be insane. And look at how much
Ethereum. Like, only I think all we need
is like
2% 5% I don't know I'm just putting a
random number out there don't quote me
quote me right so like
2 5% of this or something like that 10%
of this whole entire ethereum that could
just go to Titan X to pump up the Titan
X price that alone will send Titan X
partners to a massive rally.
Think about that okay so check out the
Titan X Spartans
dude please verify certify you know all
that stuff so that way I can feel better
about launching mine so we can all Titan
X community can launch together and get
into the Spartans
paired token I don't know the name that
I'm going to launch it with we'll figure
it out so yeah thank you guys so much
for watching I'll see you in the next
one take it easy I'm out peace.